All right, boys and girls, we have
arrived at Kawaguchiko.
Kawaguchiko, Fujikawaguchiko.
So we just checked in at our
hotel called...
I'll...
I'll write the name somewhere.
So far, I'm actually very, very
pleasantly surprised.
I booked it pretty much last minute.
Now, it doesn't have sort of the
Mount Fuji view by the lake,
But it does have the lake view, and it's a
very pretty lake in my opinion.
And honestly, it's only like
probably a 10, 20 minutes walk
to the northern side
of sort of like the little
lake area we're in,
and from there, I'm pretty sure you
can get like a view of Mount Fuji.
So we're probably gonna do that.
We got this Japanese traditional room.
It was the only room they have left,
so it was a little bit more
on the expensive end,
I think it's quite worth it.
So we're just gonna like pack out
some few stuff and then head out.
Our full first day
in Fuji starts tomorrow.
So yeah, excited to be at Fuji
for the first time.
Glad to be here and spend the next
two days here to explore.
All right guys, so just spent
a good hour or more
just taking different shots of Mount Fuji
So it's now time to head back,
find some dinner,
probably some pizza.
I found like a really decent pizza spot.
I've just been having Japanese
food for the entire trip.
So I'll be happy with some Italiano.
Lisa, what did you think of Mount Fuji?
Was it worth it?
Yes,
yeah, it's a big thumbs up from us.
We've all seen images and videos
of Mount Fuji.
But you don't really get
a proper sense of anything
unless you experience it in real life.
So I think that's what travel
is all about.
You can see all the videos that I make,
the videos that other creators make.
In the end, you really have to
go there yourself guys.
You have to experience this yourself.
It's just not the same
watching a video.
So travel to Japan,
come to Fuji,
that's an order.
The pizza restaurant is closed.
I have to find something else.
And now we found a small ramen shop.
They're just making ramen out
of a little truck here.
I think they serve Hiroshima
style tonkotsu ramen.
So looking forward to it.
After a chilly, chilly day...
Nothing beats warm ramen.
Hiroshima style ramen,
tonkotsu,
Lisa got the lobster version,
which is a little bit too fishy for me
when I tasted it,
but still very good.
Good morning, everyone.
This is our first full day.
We're heading towards a bike rental shop.
And hopefully we can rent
two bikes for today.
So we can do some exploring, just
biking around the lake.
Look at that.
Mr. Fuji.
Big boy Fujisan.
The weather is super nice,
no clouds in sight.
So can't ask for better weather
and a better day,
to start our full day of exploring.
All right, guys, so this is
our bikes we just got.
Got the bikes for the full day.
Gotta return it before the shop closes
at around 8 PM, I believe.
Boys and girls, rent a bike, honestly.
Rent a bike.
This is the...
Apple strawberry
and Lisa got the vanilla blueberry one.
I will give this...
7.5 out of 10.
Yes, it's melting.
The blueberry one.
Oh my God, so much better, guys.
Get the blueberry vanilla one.
Welcome back.
This is our last full day here
in the Fuji area.
Our first stop of the day
is Oshino Hakkai,
which is this small
sort of picturesque little village.
It's very pretty, very scenic,
it's worth the stop
It's definitely a little bit of a side
trip outside of Lake Kawaguchiko,
but I think
if you're spending two days here,
definitely worth doing.
Anyways, let's check out
Oshino Hakkai.